History is made by those who break the rules.
Men of Honor is a drama film directed by George Tillman Jr..
Against formidable odds -- and an old-school diving
instructor embittered by the U.S.
Navy's new, less prejudicial policies -- Carl Brashear sets his sights on becoming the
Navy's first African-American master diver in this uplifting true story.
Their relationship starts out on the rocks, but fate ultimately conspires to bring
the men together into a setting of mutual respect, triumph and honor.
Master Chief Leslie W. Sunday ('Billy'), played by Robert De Niro.
Senior Chief Carl Brashear, played by Cuba Gooding Jr..
Gwen Sunday, played by Charlize Theron.
Jo, played by Aunjanue Ellis-Taylor.
'Mr. Pappy', played by Hal Holbrook.
GM1 Snowhill, played by Michael Rapaport.
Men of Honor (released in the UK and Ireland as Men of Honour) is a
2000 American drama film directed by George Tillman Jr.
and starring Robert De Niro and Cuba Gooding Jr.
The film is inspired by the true story of Master Chief Petty Officer Carl Brashear,
the first African American master diver in the United States Navy.
The tone is uplifting and emotional.